James Cameron

Social Media Manager

PHONE LINKS

5612551937

EMAIL

guwopinfo@gmail.com

Profile

Twitter, LinkedIn

I am James Cameron. I am 18 years old from Palm Beach Gardens, Florida and I specialize in

social media management. I have worked with many esports organizations and creators and continue to do so presently. I am a proven social media manager who demonstrates many skills and aspires to be the best. I plan to take on more within an organization to achieve goals through

my hard work and dedication as a social media manager.

Education

Jun 2020 - Present PALM BEACH GARDENS Palm Beach State College

Business

I am a freshman college student at Palm Beach Community College and am pursuing a

bachelor's degree in business.

Skills

Brand Awareness

Digital Marketing

Business Development Strategies

Market Growth & Expansion

Communication Skills

Online Advertising

Community Development

Project Management Skills

Community Engagement

Social Media Management

Content Research & Development

Time Management Skills

Employment History

May 2020 - Oct 2020

Social Media Manager

QaziCo LLC

QaziCo LLC was an esports organization that started in May 2020. While in QaziCo, I managed the team's Instagram, Twitter, TikTok, and YouTube. I grew their socials very well and eventually gained them thousands of followers in just a few months. Unfortunately, this organization did

not succeed financially and had to shut down.

Nov 2020 - Feb 2021

Social Media Manager

Team Pure

Team Pure is another esports organization I started working with starting in November of 2020. As their social media manager, I managed the organization's Instagram, Twitter, and YouTube. In just a few months, I have gained them over 5,000 followers.

Nov 2020 - Feb 2021

Social Media Intern

Overtime Gaming

Within my internship with Overtime Gaming, I was given various tasks that involved content that would be issued to the brand's socials including Twitter, TikTok, and Instagram.

Clients I Have Worked with as a Social Media Manager

Dec 2020 - Present

Spaiidz

Spaildz is a content creator who uploads Fortnite content to YouTube. Spaildz has a very impressive following of over 500,000. My job as his social media manager is to grow his Instagram to the best of my ability.

Dec 2020 - Jan 2021

RichHomieQuinn

RichHomieQuinn is a streamer, content creator, and Fortnite competitive player. Quinn has a following of over 200,000 and continues to grow every day. He is also apart of Xtra Gaming, a very well-known gaming organization. My job as his social media manager is to grow his TikTok to the best of my ability while posting twice a day.

Jan 2021 - Present

Sly

Sly is a content creator who produces content on many platforms like Twitch, YouTube, and TikTok. Sly has a total following of over 400,000. My job as his social media manager is to grow his Instagram to the best of my ability.